(Bernadette:)Well, thanks again.
(Sheldon:)You're welcome.
(Sheldon:)And any time you need a break
(Sheldon:)from being
Bernadette the Pregnant,
(Sheldon:)Bernatrix the Warrior Queen
is here waiting.
(Bernadette:)I might just take
you up on that.
(Sheldon:)Well, mind you now,
(Sheldon:)that offer's only good
until the third trimester.
(Sheldon:)I can't risk getting
amniotic fluid on my spot.
(Raj:)Hey, dude, you're
killing me with Claire.
(Zack:)What are you talking about?
(scoffs) I mean,
come on, look at you.
(Raj:)You're classically handsome,
you've got a swimmer's body.
(Raj:)Next to you,
I look like me.
(Zack:)Oh, man,
I didn't mean to do that.
(Zack:)But I do appreciate you
recognizing my swimmer's body.
(Zack:)Which, incidentally,
(Zack:)I got from playing
Marco Polo at the YMCA.
(Raj:)Yeah, okay, just...
do me a favor
(Raj:)and stop talking about
how great Claire is.
(Zack:)Anything for you,
my little foreign friend.
(Claire:)So, I got to ask,
(Claire:)does Raj bring around
other girls?